router-switch.com 2019-06-21

# Privacy Policy

**Last Updated: June 2018. We have updated our privacy policy to meet new data protection regulations including GDPR. See   here**.

Your privacy is important to us. This privacy statement explains the personal data router-switch.com processes, how router-switch.com processes it, and for what purposes.

Router-switch.com (HongKong Yejian Technologies Co., Ltd) is committed to respecting and protecting your online privacy and recognise your need for appropriate protection and management of any personally identifiable information (Personal Data) that you may share with us.

## Personal Data We Collect

Router-switch.com collects personal data from you, through our interactions with you. You provide some of this data directly, and we get some of it by collecting data about your interactions, use and experiences. We also obtain data about you from third parties.

Router-switch.com only collects and uses personal data which is necessary to comply with our legal obligations and to assist us to administer our business and provide you with the services you request.

Router-switch.com collects personal data from you, through your registration on our site, placing orders, subscription to our newsletter or getting a quote. When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter the following information: your name, country, company, e-mail, shipping address, billing address, phone number and other relevant data. You may, however, also visit our site anonymously.

## Personal Data We Use

Router-switch.com uses the data we collect to provide you better services user experiences. In particular, we use data to:

Provide the service or carry out the transactions you request.

Improve customer service and develop our products.

Provide you with our latest information and IT news.

Advertise and market to you. Promote our products and make recommendations, which includes sending promotional communications, targeting advertising, and presenting you relevant offers.

We also use the data to operate our business, which includes analyzing our performance, meeting our legal obligations, developing our workforce, and doing research.

In carrying out these purposes, we combine data we collect from different contexts (for example, from your use of network products) or obtain from third parties to give you a more seamless, consistent, and personalized experience, to make informed business decisions, and for other legitimate purposes.

## Disclosure of Personal Data

We do not share your personal data without your consent or to complete any transaction or provide any product you have requested or authorized.

Router-switch.com is focusing its efforts to ensure that they handle this Personal Data in light with the high standards of applicable data protection rules, including **GDPR.** From May 25th, 2018, the Directive and local legislation based on the Directive will be replaced by the Regulations (EU) 2016/679 of the European Parliament and of the Council of 27 April 2016 on the protection of natural persons with regard to the processing of Personal Data and on the free movement of such data, known as the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR). We recognise that ensuring GDPR standards are embedded in our day to day operations where we handle Personal Data of EU citizens is a key GDPR compliance requirement.

We reserve the right to disclose any such personal data if required to do so by law, or in the good faith belief that such action is reasonably necessary to comply with applicable law, or protect the rights, property or safety of router-switch.com, its employees, customers, or the public.

## Access & Control Your Personal Data

You can also make choices about router-switch.com’s collection and use of your data. You can control your personal data that router-switch.com has obtained. You have the right to access, correct, or delete the personal data that we collect. You are also entitled to restrict or object, at any time, to the further processing of your personal data.

You have the right to receive your personal data in a structured and standard format and, where technically feasible, the right to have your personal data transmitted directly to a third party.

To protect the privacy and the security of your personal data, we may request data from you to enable us to confirm your identity and right to access such information, as well as to search for and provide you with the personal data we maintain.

You can always choose whether you wish to receive promotional emails, messages from router-switch.com. You can also access and clear your data through the router-switch.com privacy dashboard.

## Cookies

Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser (if you have allowed it via your settings). This enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.

We use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart, understand and save your preferences for future visits and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools for you in the future.

We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are however not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us directly conduct and improve our business. We use, for example, Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc. (“Google”) to help us better understand how users engage with our website. Google Analytics uses cookies in order to collect information on the usage of our website. This information is used to compile reports and create services to help us improve our website and the services associated with it. The reports disclose website trends without identifying individual visitors. The information generated by the Google cookie about your use of our website (including your IP address) may be transmitted to and stored by Google on servers in the United States. Google may also transfer this information to third parties where required to do so by law, or where such third parties process the information on Google's behalf. Google will not associate your IP address with any other data held by Google.

On some pages of our website, third parties that provide applications through our website may set their own cookies in order to provide services, track the success of their applications or customize applications for you. For example, when you share content using a social media sharing button such as Facebook, LinkedIn or Twitter, the social network that has created the button will record that you have done this. Because of how cookies work, we cannot access these cookies nor can the third parties access the data in cookies used by us.

You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies via your browser settings. Like most websites, if you turn your cookies off, some of our services may not function properly. However, you can still place orders by contacting customer service at [cisco@router-switch.com](mailto:cisco@router-switch.com)

## Protect Your Personal Data

You are responsible for your own username and password safety and security on router-switch.com. We recommend choosing a strong password and changing it frequently. Please do not use the same login details (email and password) across multiple websites.

We do implement a variety of security measures including offering the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be stored on our servers.

Our servers and website are security scanned and fully verified externally by McAfee Secure from Symantec on a daily basis to protect you online.

## Changes to Our Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, and update the Privacy Policy modification date above.

## Contact Us

If you have any further questions regarding the personal data router-switch.com collects, or how we use it, then please feel free to contact us by email at: [ccie-support@router-switch.com.](mailto:ccie-support@router-switch.com)
